Another world… as close as the beat of your heart
Photographing Fairies is a mystery, fantasy,
drama film directed by Nick Willing.
Photographer Charles Castle is numbed with grief
following the death of his beautiful bride.
He goes off to war, working in the trenches as a photographer.
Following the war and still in grief Charles is given some
photographs purporting to be of fairies.
His search for the truth leads him to Burkinwell, a
seemingly peaceful village seething with secrets
Charles Castle, played by Toby Stephens.
Linda, played by Emily Woof.
Rev. Templeton, played by Ben Kingsley.
Beatrice Templeton, played by Frances Barber.
Doctor, played by Bernard Gallagher.
Roy, played by Phil Davis.
Photographing Fairies is a 1997 British fantasy film based on
Steve Szilagyi's 1992 novel Photographing Fairies.
The film explores some of the themes of folklore, such as possession,
paganism, animism, hallucinogens, parapsychology and fairies.
It was inspired by the Cottingley Fairies hoax, and was
released in the United Kingdom on 19 September 1997.
The film explores themes of based on novel or book,
photographer, loss of loved one, fairy, grieving widower.
The tone is emotional and mind_bending.